<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://czi-catalystproject.github.io/catalyst-project//catalyst-project/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://czi-catalystproject.github.io/catalyst-project//catalyst-project/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-01-18T09:46:57+00:00</updated><id>https://czi-catalystproject.github.io/catalyst-project//catalyst-project/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Catalyst Project</title><subtitle>A simple, whitespace theme for academics. Based on [*folio](https://github.com/bogoli/-folio) design. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Catalyst Project offering for Communities</title><link href="https://czi-catalystproject.github.io/catalyst-project//catalyst-project/blog/2024/project-offering/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Catalyst Project offering for Communities"/><published>2024-01-17T16:40:16+00:00</published><updated>2024-01-17T16:40:16+00:00</updated><id>https://czi-catalystproject.github.io/catalyst-project//catalyst-project/blog/2024/project-offering</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://czi-catalystproject.github.io/catalyst-project//catalyst-project/blog/2024/project-offering/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="introduction">Introduction</h2> <p>The Catalyst Project is a project funded by the Chan Zuckerberg Initiative aimed at providing cloud infrastructure to biomedical communities in Africa and Latin America. The Catalyst Project will onboard 10 biomedical communities in each of Africa and Latin America by April, 2024. To achieve the aim of the project, the project team is composed of seven (7) organisations that all share an interest in promoting open science. These organisations include 2i2c, OLS, The Carpentries, MetaDocencia, CSCCE, IOI and CCAD. To learn more about these organisations and their roles on the Catalyst Project please visit our <a href="https://czi-catalystproject.github.io/catalyst-project/#partner-projects">homepage</a>.</p> <p>Providing cloud infrastructure to communities will include ACCESS and GUIDANCE. ACCESS to the infrastructure and GUIDANCE on using the infrastructure. The main offering of the Catalyst Project to communities is thus ACCESS to cloud infrastructure and GUIDANCE on how to use the infrastructure to promote open science.</p> <h2 id="access-to-cloud-infrastructure">Access to cloud infrastructure</h2> <p>The Catalyst Project will provide biomedical communities in Africa and Latin America ACCESS to cloud infrastructure for the duration of the project. Currently the support to the infrastructure will end by 31st October, 2025. The project team is working to ensure that at least each community has access to the infrastructure for at least 18 months.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample-posts"/><category term="2i2c"/><category term="OLS"/><category term="CSCCE"/><category term="MetaDocencia"/><category term="Carpentries"/><category term="IOI"/><category term="CCAD"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The blogpost describes the offering of the Catalyst project to the communities onboarded]]></summary></entry></feed>